Yunlin Li

Mobile: 07900918268, Email: ling428lyl@gmail.com, GitHub: ling428lyl (github.com)

SUMMARY

A versatile and creative game designer/developer skilled in Unity, Maya and related VR/AR technologies, with a foundation in Network Engineering and a Master's in Immersive Technologies. Demonstrated ability to integrate both creative and technical aspects of game design and game art within various experience in VR & AR development, game design & development, 3D modeling & animations and web development.

EDUCATION

University of Bristol 09/2023-12/2024

Master of Science in Immersive Technologies (Virtual and Augmented Reality)

Core Modules: Virtual Environment Design, Immersive Interaction and Audio Design, Augmenting the Real World, Immersive Games Design and Production

Guangzhou University 09/2019-06/2023

Bachelor of Engineering in Network Engineering

Grade: 88

Grade: 90

Predicted Grade: 65

Core Modules: Database Principles, Data Structures, Object Oriented Programming (C++), Web Application Technology, Software Engineering, etc.

Online Course: Creative Programming for Digital Media & Mobile Apps

06/2022-08/2022

Organised by Goldsmiths, University of London

SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

Skills: Unity, Maya, Procreate, RealityCapture, Photoshop, C#, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Vue.js, Node.js, MongoDB, MySQL, C++.

Awards: Guangzhou University 3rd Prize Scholarship (2019-2020 & 2021-2022).

Language: Native in Cantonese & Mandarin; English (IELTS-7.0).

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

VR Graffiti Stealth Game 06/2024-08/2024

Participant, Coursework of Creative and Immersive Project (Postgraduate Graduation Project)

- Designed all aspects of the game (e.g. mechanics, narratives and levels) with the other member.
- Created different animations, poses and trigger logics of the VR hand models according to different interactions.
- Implemented UI design, spray cans interactions and the paint mechanic using VR techniques in Unity. Used Behaviour Tree to implement the AI behaviours.

AR Application of Children Story Book

02/2024-04/2024

Participant, Coursework of Augmenting the Real World (68/100)

- Designed the UI and Created the first scene of *The Gruffalo* story in Unity using AR techniques (e.g. tracking, raycast, light estimation, etc.).
- Used RealityCapture to create the virtual 3D model of the character and created the animation in Maya.
- Ensured the scene cohesion and demonstrated the application with other teammates.

VR Zombie Survival Shooting Game

02/2024-04/2024

Participant, Coursework of Immersive Games Design and Production (64/100)

- Designed and implemented the game in Unity with teammates (version control and feature integration in GitLab).
- Implemented the game tutorial and UI design. Created different animations, poses and trigger logics of the VR hand models according to different interactions.

VR Symphonic Planets Interactive Experience

02/2024-04/2024

Participant, Coursework of Immersive Interaction and Audio Design (65/100)

Designed the realistic materials, particle effects of the element balls and set terrain generation in the main planet

according to different elements in the game.

Used different instruments to compose the soundtracks based on the traits of the element balls in the game.

Virtual Environment Design of a Tea Shop

10/2023-12/2023

Coursework of Virtual Environment Design (70/100)

- Took reference pictures and modelled a virtual environment in Maya, to accurately recreate a tea shop in Bristol.
- Modelled the furniture, decorations and plants, applied textures and designed lighting of the environment.

Campus lost and found mini-program design and implementation

01/2023-04/2023

Personal Undergraduate Graduation Project (85/100)

- Understood relevant topics and research. Analysed feasibility and requirements of the system and designed the functional modules, interface and database.
- Implemented various functions (e.g. login, upload & post, classify, search, comment, etc.) of the mini-program and the backend management system using Vue.js, Node.js, MongoDB, JavaScript etc.

Industry Practice Project Computer Science Track

02/2022-03/2022

Part-time Assistant (Remote), Tencent Video, Platform and Content Group

- > Communicated with the supervisor to understand the business requirements and clarify job responsibilities.
- Assisted in optimising the algorithm efficiency. Conceptualised the problems into data structures with C++, simulated real-world data processing and designed algorithms to enhance computing efficiency.

INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE

Agricultural Bank of China (Guangzhou Branch)

09/2022-10/2022

Front-end Development Intern

- Collaborated with team (version control in SVN) to complete an E-commerce management system based on Vue.js, discussed with the product manager to determine the project requirements and overall project design.
- > Designed static webpages and programmed interfaces for front-end and back-end interactions, implemented and improved the functionality in the requirements and tested the project.

Guangdong Planning and Designing Institute of Telecommunications Co., Ltd No.2 Branch 07/2022-09/2022 Front-end Development Intern

- Produced front-end pages (e.g. order management, product management, etc.).
- Used different JavaScript frameworks based on the current project (Vue and React), cooperated and communicated with the back-end personnel to conduct large-screen data visualisation and displayed the data dynamically, which improved the efficiency of business decision-making.

CREATIVE PRACTICE

Design of the Guangzhou University Postgraduate Admission Letter

04/2022

> Designed and produced a creative work of postgraduate admission letter in Procreate and Photoshop, including the envelope based on the traits of the campus and the city culture.

Colour 60-day Challenge Vol.8

03/2022-05/2022

Completed one colour painting each day in Procreate and Photoshop. Learnt about colour theories and analysed different photographers' works & masterpieces.